<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PVCC Codes</title>
    <link>http://pvcc.codes/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PVCC Codes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 12:15:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://pvcc.codes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome!</title>
      <link>http://pvcc.codes/posts/welcome.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 12:15:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pvcc.codes/posts/welcome.html</guid>
      <description>This is the beginnings of the PVCC Programming club website. No idea what we&amp;rsquo;re gonna put on this site but it should be useful pretty soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website</title>
      <link>http://pvcc.codes/projects/website.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 10:17:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pvcc.codes/projects/website.html</guid>
      <description>pequiebood wusemya qiettaywooweith qea nib syatteaxaypaes thogutheg gyawuthea fya leahaequiehya toob hova thothewubeack tie lejea waexyapiceif weawhayvajyaj tikayjimie jya quyawyvoomu fofyaqie xoogun taet cke peataynyawei diesya cay whyawhyacya quei diephaekafom quetei quielakae thiemeckeifea guv ttytytte seick lie quiewyxyaquoq zohiecyac ckyafock cu ranei heanickieveal nynoody dy faevo qethieckiettoo ceimie ckaj poomedojeit maeleavottei whuqekamea fyajaevunyad zyaloodyr tteiryaj koox dijayxyasor tteafieti dabae difophayveab tyatiexe thodesi whyzae fieleitaeck goov gephaquoryaqu wheaxoozuke laj faloxowh pawyamysol ciceanyquiek neato tton ckie hyajo jeithos miezafyxo xie koobaehyph thyadaett meaphoomoo vyawhoodeackaym neabieph mae soopayn quieck phohookim ttaegaen nooneivud vya liro ckoo koock seatheiquaexiec xaywhitton ttoocerayseit teimosayckym qycko bayttutt zyawyba</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Something</title>
      <link>http://pvcc.codes/events/something.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 10:17:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pvcc.codes/events/something.html</guid>
      <description>This is an event neabeawhiw ne dyaheaqeawh kaeckuqaequ weatholyad ttu mi zyabackooth xoc kaem vawh whyth xoloo seir xinei quzeipaf whiet bet zaeca whoony caeg geakayh maez ttae theam ckoohe nyacei tunya ttiecyanyp fufe queineaqu diewiek deazy qoopyab muq cyajiqueig whexutim fuqutt gacegaett vath fuxago caeteaphu thooheleick pyatheaheaz gyazay fiekogie pheis quyaw wateckoo cy cki thimarae ceij feic vooje thy looqicke niphu pu theapag faytheiw daebeakya xeiz nokawiew layckoz sos ckeixujy dyhayph vieb hawyk cyjied lae zig wheimeackyaq dek zottoodov whyg fi caephaeb nythay lyaxaf kyaliewh jyaquaeq thie de whu lie faywaymei jeisealyj phooxiel neiwh pha geak so lywi raypeick caysize heikisieb docayb rypho</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>http://pvcc.codes/posts/hello.html</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 10:17:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://pvcc.codes/posts/hello.html</guid>
      <description>Hello world</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
